// Define arrays for easy, medium, and hard questions
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Hello?",
        answer: "B. Kia Ora",
        options: [
            "A. Papa",
            "B. Kia Ora",
            "C. Manaakitanga",
            "D. Haere ra"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Family?",
        answer: "A. Whanau",
        options: [
            "A. Whanau",
            "B. Waka",
            "C. Kikorangi",
            "D. Pango"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Love?",
        answer: "A. Aroha",
        options: [
            "A. Aroha",
            "B. Ahiahi Pai",
            "C. Papura",
            "D. Parauri"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Food?",
        answer: "B. Kai",
        options: [
            "A. Ngako",
            "B. Kai",
            "C. Mea Atu",
            "D. Roopu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Mountain?",
        answer: "A. Maunga",
        options: [
            "A. Maunga",
            "B. Ua",
            "C. Aotearoa",
            "D. Koropiko"
        ]
    }
];

let mediumQuestions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Land?",
        answer: "B. Whenua",
        options: [
            "A. Rangatira",
            "B. Whenua",
            "C. Whare",
            "D. Tangata"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the Māori word for River?",
        answer: "A. Awa",
        options: [
            "A. Awa",
            "B. Moana",
            "C. Wai",
            "D. Rangi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Hear?",
        answer: "A. Rongo",
        options: [
            "A. Rongo",
            "B. Whakarongo Mai",
            "C. Hapa",
            "D. Parauri"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the Māori word for You?",
        answer: "B. Koe",
        options: [
            "A. Ahau",
            "B. Koe",
            "C. Matou",
            "D. Ratou"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Earth?",
        answer: "A. Papatūānuku",
        options: [
            "A. Papatūānuku",
            "B. Tangaroa",
            "C. Tāne",
            "D. Rangi"
        ]
    }
];

let hardQuestions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Carving?",
        answer: "B. Whakairo",
        options: [
            "A. Tekau",
            "B. Whakairo",
            "C. Tāniko",
            "D. Pango"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Weaving?",
        answer: "A. Raranga",
        options: [
            "A. Raranga",
            "B. Poti",
            "C. Moana",
            "D. Ngā mihi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Clothing?",
        answer: "A. Kakahu",
        options: [
            "A. Kakahu",
            "B. Māra",
            "C. Rākau",
            "D. Matimati"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Plant?",
        answer: "B. Tipu",
        options: [
            "A. Whangi",
            "B. Tipu",
            "C. Tī",
            "D. Tuhi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the Māori word for Lieutenant?",
        answer: "A. Rutene",
        options: [
            "A. Rutene",
            "B. Ringa",
            "C. Hauhautanga",
            "D. Whanui"
        ]
    }
];